<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="statement_array">
        <item>Look, if you had one shot, one opportunity</item>
        <item>To seize everything you ever wanted, in one moment</item>
        <item>Would you capture it or just let it slip?</item>
        <item>His palms are sweaty, knees weak, arms are heavy</item>
        <item>Theres vomit on his sweater already, moms spaghetti</item>
        <item>Hes nervous, but on the surface he looks calm and ready to drop bombs</item>
        <item>but he keeps on forgettin what he wrote down</item>
        <item>The whole crowd goes so loud</item>
        <item>He opens his mouth, but the words wont come out</item>
        <item>The clocks run out, times up, over, blow!</item>
        <item>Oh, there goes Rabbit, he choked</item>
        <item>He\'s so mad, but he won\'t give up that easy, nope</item>
        <item>He won\'t have it, he knows his whole back\'s to these ropes</item>
        <item>He knows that, but he\'s broke</item>
        <item>When he goes back to his mobile home, that\'s when it\'s</item>
        <item>He better go capture this moment and hope it don\'t pass him</item>
        <item>You better lose yourself in the music, the moment</item>
        <item>You only get one shot, do not miss your chance to blow</item>
        <item>This opportunity comes once in a lifetime yo</item>
        <item>You better lose yourself in the music, the moment</item>
        <item>The Prime Minister may recommend the dismissal of a State Councilor to the President.</item>
        <item>Members of the National Assembly perform their duties in accordance with their conscience, prioritizing national interests.</item>
        <item>When a judge is unable to perform their duties due to significant mental or physical impairment, they may retire according to the law.</item>
        <item>All citizens have the freedom of learning and art.</item>
        <item>The proceedings and judgments of trials are made public.</item>
        <item>The Board of Audit and Inspection is composed of 5 to 11 auditors, including the head.</item>
        <item>The economic order of the Republic of Korea is based on respecting the freedom and creativity of individuals and businesses.</item>
        <item>Girls\' Generation\'s activities have achieved great popularity and success not only in Korea but also internationally.</item>
        <item>They are the original girl group that sparked the Hallyu wave in Japan.</item>
        <item>They, along with BIGBANG, played a significant role in expanding the domestic and international idol music market of K-POP.</item>
        <item>They have paved the way for junior idols in various musical aspects, becoming a role model.</item>
        <item>In the \'Top 10 Best K-POP Girl Groups in the Last 10 Years\' selected by Billboard in 2017, they took the first place, earning the title 'K-POP Emperor'.</item>
        <item>From the founding of Joseon to the fourth king, Sejong, Shin Gae served in various positions.</item>
        <item>From October 10, 1432, to February 10, 1446, Shin Gae directly participated in state affairs, speaking mainly about his diary.</item>
        <item>It is included in the collection of Shin Gae\'s writings, Injae Collection.</item>
        <item>A person working for a national agency or local government.</item>
        <item>The concept of a civil servant began to be widely used with the establishment of a democratic political order.</item>
        <item>In our country, civil servants are defined as the servants of the people.</item>
        <item>Presidents, judges, and members of the National Assembly are all civil servants.</item>
        <item>General civil servants handle tasks related to technology, research, or general administration.</item>
        <item>Except for career civil servants, the remaining civil servants are called special career civil servants.</item>
        <item>Most of the personnel in general administrative agencies are general civil servants.</item>
        <item>Everyone was a child at first. However, not many adults remember that.</item>
        <item>A bird struggles to come out of the egg.</item>
        <item>Hello world</item>
        <item>I spent a shameful life. I cannot understand the essence of human life.</item>
        <item>When you desperately want something, the whole universe conspires to help you achieve your wish.</item>
        <item>As we emerged from the long tunnel of the border, it was a different country.</item>
        <item>Even in a life chewed up and spit out by someone, I will endure and persistently extract the remaining morsels.</item>
        <item>There are three things that humans cannot hide: coughs, poverty, and love.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
